In this video, we are going to continue or discussion of run time organization by
在本视频中，我们将通过以下方式继续或讨论运行时组织
talking about how compilers handle global variables and heap data structures. Let's
谈论编译器如何处理全局变量和堆数据结构。我们走吧
start by talking about global variables. The basic properties of the global
从讨论全局变量开始。全局的基本属性
variables that all the references point to the same object. That what it means to be
所有引用都指向同一对象的变量。这就是它的意义所在
global And for this reason, we can't store all the variables in the activation record
全局的，因此，我们不能存储激活记录中的所有变量
because the activation record if, of course, is the allocated. When the
因为当然，如果激活记录是分配的。当
activation completes and that would be the allocated global variable. So. The way
激活完成，这将是分配的全局变量。所以。这条路
that little variables are implemented is that all global are signed the fix address
实现的小变量是所有全局变量都用固定地址签名
once And these variables with fixed addresses are said to be statically
这些具有固定地址的变量称为静态变量
allocated because they're allocated essentially at compiled times. So the
分配是因为它们基本上是在编译时分配的。因此，
compiler decides where they going to live and then they will live there in all
编译器决定他们将住在哪里，然后他们将全部住在那里
executions of the program And depending on the language, there may be other
程序的执行，根据语言的不同，可能还有其他
statically allocated values and we'll actually see some later on but they behave
静态分配的值，我们稍后会看到一些，但它们的行为
just the same as global variables. So I think global variables changes our run
就像全局变量一样。所以我认为全局变量改变了我们的运行
time organization picture a little bit. First we have the code as before, and
有点时间组织图。首先，我们有和以前一样的代码，然后
then, immediately after the code is typically all of the static data. So these
然后，紧跟在代码后面的通常是所有的静电数据。所以这些都是
are the global variables and other static object, things that have fixed addresses
是全局变量和其他静电对象，都是有固定地址的东西
for the duration of the execution of the program and then the stack comes after
在程序执行期间，然后堆栈在
that. So the stack will start at the end of the static data area and grow towards
那。因此，堆栈将从静电数据区的末尾开始，并向
the end of the program's allocated memory. Trying out to the heat, any value that,
程序分配的内存的末尾。在高温下试一试，任何值，
that outlives the procedure that creates it also cannot be stored in the activation
它的存留时间超过创建它的过程，也不能存储在激活中
record. Let's take a look at this example. So here we have a procedure foo
录音。让我们看一下这个例子。所以这里我们有一个过程foo
and let's take a look at the activation record or frame for foo. Now let's
让我们来看看foo的激活记录或帧。现在让我们
say that a foo allocates a bar object and that we're going to store that object in
假设foo分配了一个bar对象，我们将把该对象存储在
foo activation And now when this method returns, of course the activation record
FOO激活，现在当此方法返回时，当然是激活记录
would be de-allocated so the bar obj ect will also go away but that won't work here
将被取消分配，因此BAR对象也将消失，但这在这里不起作用
because notice that the dynamically allocated object - the object we allocated
因为请注意动态分配的对象-我们分配的对象
during the execution of foo - is also the results of foo so this has to be, this has
在执行foo的过程中-也是foo的结果，所以这必须是，这是
to be accessible to foo's caller. After [inaudible] exits And so what that means
以便于Foo的呼叫者访问。在[听不见]出口之后，那是什么意思？
is that this borrow object and all dynamically allocated data has to be
这个借用对象和所有动态分配的数据必须
stored some place other than the activation record and language is what
存储激活记录和语言之外的其他位置是什么
dynamically allocated data generally use a heap for that purpose. At this
为此，动态分配的数据通常使用堆。在这个时候
point, we can summarize the different kinds of data that the language of
这一点，我们可以总结出语言的不同类型的数据
implementation has to deal with. First there is the code and in many languages, I
实施必须处理。首先是代码，在许多语言中，我
shouldn't say most. In many languages. The code is fixed size and read only. I mean
不应该说的最多。在许多语言中。代码是固定大小的，并且是只读的。我是说
that the compiler creates all the code that will be used in the execution of the
编译器创建将在执行
program and that could be allocated once. It should say that there are many
程序，并且可以分配一次。应该说有很多
languages also were this is not true and code can be dynamically created at one
语言也认为这不是真的，代码可以一次动态创建
time. The static area. Would contain data with six addresses and this would be
时间到了。静电地区。将包含具有六个地址的数据，这将是
things like global variables and this is also typically fixed size and it was maybe
比如全局变量，这通常也是固定的大小，它可能
readable and writable as opposed to the code which I generally don't want to be
可读性和可写性，而不是我通常不想要的代码
able to write. And then a stack is used to contain an activation record for each
会写字。然后使用堆栈来包含每个对象的激活记录
currently active procedure and the activation record is generally fixed size
当前活动过程和激活记录通常是固定大小
so each activation record for each particular kind of procedure has a fixed
因此，每种特定类型过程的每个激活记录都有一个固定的
size and this will contain all the local information, the local variables
大小，这将包含所有本地信息、本地变量
contemporaries that needed to execute a particular activation. And finally, the
需要执行特定激活的同时代人。最后，
heap is for everything else. So the heap is just for all the data that doesn't fit
堆是用来处理其他所有事情的。所以堆只适用于所有不适合的数据
into other categories. This includes all of the dynamically allocated data And if
归入其他类别。这包括所有动态分配的数据，如果
you are familiar with C, then the heap in C is managed by the programmer using
您熟悉C，然后C中的堆由程序员使用
[inaudible] in Java, you have new. For dynamically allocating data and then
[听不见]在爪哇，你有了新的。用于动态分配数据，然后
garbage collection actually takes care of reclaiming data from the heap that is no
垃圾收集实际上负责从堆中回收不为
longer used. Now many lang uage implementations use both the heap and the
用得更久了。现在，许多语言实现同时使用堆和
stack and there is a little bit of an issue here because both the heap and the
堆栈，这里有一个小问题，因为堆和
stack grow. And so we have to take care that they don't grow into each and step on
堆栈增长。所以我们必须小心，不要让它们长到每一只脚上
each other's data And there is a very nice and simple solution to this and as a start
每个人的数据，有一个非常好的和简单的解决方案，并作为一个开始
to heap and the stack at opposite ends of memory and let them grow towards each
将堆和堆栈放在内存的相反两端，并让它们朝着各自的方向增长
other. So, let's take another look at our Runtime Organization picture And just for
其他的。那么，让我们再看一看我们的运行时组织图，只是为了
review, first we have the code and then we have the static data. And then we have the
回顾一下，首先我们有代码，然后我们有静电的数据。然后我们就有了
stack which grows towards in this case the high address allocated to the program And,
在这种情况下朝着分配给程序的高地址增长的堆栈，
notice that the stack doesn't necessarily just grow as procedure three terms, stack
请注意，堆栈并不一定像过程三项堆栈那样增长
will also shrink. So as the program runs the stack will get bigger or smaller
也会缩小。因此，当程序运行时，堆栈将变得更大或更小
depending on how many procedures are currently running. And the heap will start
取决于当前正在运行的过程数。然后堆将启动
at the other end of memory and grow towards the lower address and so we
在内存的另一端，并朝着较低的地址增长，因此我们
allocate objects we'll be allocating from the back memory or the end of the memory
分配我们将从后台内存或内存末尾分配的对象
allocated the program up towards the top of stack And If these two points have ever
将程序分配到堆栈顶部，如果这两个点
become equal and whether the two pointers. So, we have a stack allocation pointer
变得相等，以及这两个指针是否相等。因此，我们有一个堆栈分配指针
which says where we are going to allocate the next stack frame. And we have a heap
这表明我们将在哪里分配下一个堆栈帧。我们有一堆
allocation point where it says where will allocate the next object if we have
分配点，它告诉我们，如果有，将在哪里分配下一个对象
another dynamically allocated object. As long as one of these two pointers don't
另一个动态分配的对象。只要这两个指针中的一个不
cross, as long as it never become equal then the program has memory to either add
交叉，只要它永远不会变得相等，那么程序就有内存可以相加
another stack frame or another dynamically allocated object and the program can
另一堆栈帧或另一动态分配的对象，并且该程序可以
continue away. If these programs ever become equal then the program is in fact
继续走吧。如果这些程序曾经变得平等，那么程序实际上是
out of memory and at that point the run time system will abort the program or try
内存不足，此时运行时系统将中止程序或尝试
to get more memory from the operating or take some other course of action to deal
从操作中获得更多内存或采取其他措施来处理
with the fact. If there is no there is no more memory But as long as these two
事实是。如果没有，就没有更多的内存，但只要这两个
pointers don't cross, notice that this design Allows the heap and the stack to
指针不会交叉，请注意，此设计允许堆和堆栈
share this, this data area in whatever way suits the program best. So, this same
以最适合程序的方式共享此数据区。所以，这也是一样的
design without any changes will work for programs that needed a lot of heap and
无需任何更改的设计将适用于需要大量堆和
only a little stack and for programs that need a lot of stack and only a little heap
只有很小的堆栈，对于需要很多堆栈和只需要很少堆的程序来说
and things will have a rough balance between stack and heap as long as they
堆栈和堆之间的关系会大致平衡，只要它们
don't exceed the total memory allocated to the program.
不要超过分配给程序的总内存。